Guide to the Tennesse Williams Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Tennesse Williams Papers,
1920-1983
Williams, Tennessee, 1911-1983.
7 linear ft. (614 items in 10 boxes and 10 oversize folders).
Columbia University, Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Butler Library, New York, NY, 10027.
4079626
Biographical Note
Scope and Content
Correspondence, manuscripts, photographs, set designs, programs, playbills, and other printed materials and audio recordings. The manuscripts include: "Battle of Angels"; "A Streetcar Named Desire"; "The Glass Menagerie"; "Summer and Smoke"; "Now and at the Hour of Our Death"; "Cat on a Hot Tin Roof"; "Portrait of a Girl in Glass"; "Hard Candy"; "Orpheus Descending"; "The Roman Spring of Mrs. Stone"; "You Touched Me"; "Desire and the Black Masseur"; "The Kingdom of Earth"; "The Rose Tattoo"; "The Eclipse of the Sun"; "A Balcony in Ferrara"; "Camino Real"; "The Gnadiges Fraulein"; "A Kind of Love"; "Broken Glass in the Morning"; "Suddenly Last Summer"; and "Tent Worms."
There is the typescript, with ms. corrections, of "Mes Cahiers Noirs," an unpublished diary ca. 1979.
Typewritten manuscript dating from the early 1940s of two unpublished sonnets; the mimeographed script of the David Frost interview, 21 Jan. 1970; letters to, by, or from: Herbert Machiz, Josephine Healy, Paul Bigelow, Audrey Wood (Williams' agent), Cheryl Crawford, David Diamond, James Laughlin, Glenway Wescott, Charles Feldman, Rose Williams, Edwina Williams, Edwin Dakin, Dakin Williams, and Carson McCullers; the manuscript of 9 poems, one of which "Poem for Paul" does not appear to have been published; set designs by Boris Aronson and Jo Mielziner; portrait of Williams by Leon Kroll; portrait of Rose Williams by Florence Van Steeg; portrait of Edwina Williams by Simon Branders.
Scripts for Two Character Play; This Is; Vieux Carré; A Lovely Sunday For Creve Coeur; A House Not Meant To Stand; Now The Cats With Jewelled Claws; The Youthfully Departed; A Cavalier For Milady; The Red Devil Battery Sign. Also, Tennessee Williams' "Grand": a teleplay by Trace Johnson.
Among the programs is one from The Rose Tattoo's first performance with signatures by Maureen Stapleton, Eli Wallach and others, and a Starless Air program, signed by Williams, Donald Windham, and Margaret Phillips
Director's archive for Tigertail
There is one box of books by and about Williams with annotations by Jay Leo Colt.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 6 series:
Series I: Correspondence
Series II: Works
Series III: Personal
Series IV: Works by Others
Series V: Photographs
Series VI: Audiotapes
Subjects
Aronson, Boris, 1900-1980.; Bigelow, Paul, d. 1961.; Crawford, Cheryl, 1902-1986.; Diamond, David, 1915-2005.; Kroll, Leon, 1884-1974.; Laughlin, James, 1914-1997.; Lobdell, David.; McCullers, Carson, 1917-1967.; Mielziner, Jo, 1901-1976.; Stapleton, Maureen.; Wallach, Eli, 1915-; Wescott, Glenway, 1901-1987.; Windham, Donald.; American drama--20th century.; Dramatists, American--20th century.; Short stories, American--20th century.; Articles.; Audio tapes.; Autographs.; Awards.; Catalogs.; Certificates.; Diaries.; Fiction.; Interviews.; Lithographs.; Manuscripts (literary).; Oil paintings.; Passports.; Phonograph records.; Photographs.; Playbills.; Poems.; Portraits.; Posters.; Programs.; Receipts.; Reviews.; Scrapbooks.; Scripts.; Set design drawings.; Sound recordings.; Authors, American.; Dramatists.
Access Restrictions
This collection has no restrictions.
This collection is located on-site.
Acquisition
Papers Various Gifts and purchase
05/26/1991 M-91-05-26 Annotated books Estate of Jay Leo Colt Gift
05/21/1991 M-91-05-21 Papers 487 (Brander Matthews) 7/1/91 Purchase
01/22/1996 M-96-1-11 14 TW letters to Lobdell 2293B Purchase
Alternate Formats
Manuscripts of "Battle of Angels," "The Fugitive Kind," and "Orpheus descending" are on microfilm.
Gift of the Friends of the Columbia Libraries, 1970.
Gift of Mr & Mrs Robert L. Wilbur, 1982.
Gift of the estate of Jay Leo Colt, 1991.
- Series I: Correspondence
  1907-1983. 4 linear ft. The Correspondence series is divided into: Cataloged Correspondence; Dakin Williams Files; Letters from Agents and Publishers; and General Correspondence. The first two subseries are listed item by item. The series consists of letters from friends, family, and colleagues that often deal with Williams' writings and productions.
  - Subseries I.1: Cataloged Correspondence, 1920-1982
    The letters are from friends, relatives, actors, directors, writers, and colleagues. They are arranged alphabetically by sender.
    - Ahrens, Gerhard To Tennessee Williams, Totstedt, Germany, 1963, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Anderson, Phillia and Bob To Paul Bigelow, New York, 3 Feb. 1951, (1 p. telegram) (Box A)
    - Assante, Armand To Tennessee Williams, New York, NY, 21 August 1972, (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
      [With portrait photograph and envelope]
    - Atkinson, Brooks To Tennessee Williams, New York, NY, [2 March 1958] - 9 June 1960, (3 p. 1 a.l.s., 2 t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [With envelope]
    - Bloom, Claire To Tennessee Williams, [n.p.], 17 March 1973 & 28 January 1982, (5 p. a.l.s. & t.n.) (Box A)
    - Bowles, Jane To Tennessee Williams, [Fez, Morocco], [18 March 1949], (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Bowles, Paul To Tennessee Williams, [v.p.], 11 March 1949 - 27 Dec. 1957, (8 p. 5 t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Bowles, Paul To Tennessee Williams, [v.p.], 11 May 1958 - 18 Oct. 1971, (5 pages, 5 t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [With 1 envelope, one photocopy]
    - Bowles, Paul To Tennessee Williams, v.p., 30 Mar. 1974 - n.d., (5 pages, 5 t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [With 1 envelope]
    - Bowles, Paul To Tennessee Williams, Morocco, 3 Feb 1962, (1 p.c.s.) (Box A)
    - Bowles, Paul To Peter Garland, Tangier, Morocco, 3 March 1981, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [Photocopy]
    - Boyle, Kay To Tennessee Williams, Rowayton, CT., 9 June 1958, (1 p. a.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - [Brando, Marlon] To Tennessee Williams, [n.p.], [n.d.], (2 p. t.l. ) (Box A)
      [Transcript of typed letter]
    - Brownlow, Isabel To Family, Knoxville, TN, 8 June 1937, (3 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [With envelope; Isabel was Williams's aunt]
    - Clemens, Cyril To Tennessee Williams, Kirkwood, MO., 20 March 1974, (1 p. a.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Crawford, Cheryl To William Liebling, [New York], [ca. Feb. 1952], (4 p. a.n.s.) (Box A)
      [Written on letter from Paul Bigelow to her of [Feb.] 8; With covering t.n.s. from Liebling to Bigelow, 2/12/52; With envelope]
    - Diamond, David To Cheryl Crawford, New York, 15 Jan. 1951, (1 p. telegram) (Box A)
    - Diamond, David To Paul Bigelow, New York, 16 Jan. 1951, (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Engle, Paul To Tennessee Williams, Iowa City, 24 Jan. 1957, (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Feldman, Charles and Jerry Wald To The Reverend Walter Edwin Dakin, Beverly Hills, CA, 13 Sept. 1949, (1 p. telegram) (Box A)
      [Invitation to a party for Tennessee]
    - Fischer, Louis To Tennessee Williams, Athens, Greece, n.d., (1 p. a.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Gibson, William To Tennessee Williams, Stockbridge, MA & n.p., 18 Dec. 1974 & 15 Sept. 19[??], (16 p. 1 a.l.s. & 1 t.l.s. ) (Box A)
      [With copy of 14 page memo]
    - Ginsberg, Allen To Tennessee Williams, Boulder, CO, 18 May 1982, (1 p. 1 t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Gish, Lillian To Tennessee Williams, New York, NY & [n.p.], Sept. 1962 & 9 Feb. 1963, (2 p. 1 a.l.s. & 1 t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Hellman, Lillian To Tennessee Williams, New York, NY, 7 May 1982, (1 p. 1 t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Herlihy, James Leo To Tennessee Williams, Key West, FL & n.p., 16 May - 14 June 1960., (2 p. 1 t.l.s. & 1 a.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Hoffman, Abbie To Tennessee Williams, [New York, NY], 12 Sept. [1973], (1 p. 1 a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Kazan, Elia To Tennessee Williams, v.p., n.d. - 6 Oct. 1958, (21 p. 5 t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [With 3 envelopes]
    - Kazan, Elia To Tennessee Williams, v.p., 5 Jan. 1959 - 25 April 1962, (7 p. 3 t.l.s. & 2 t.l.) (Box A)
    - Kazan, Elia To Tennessee Williams, v.p., 19 Oct. 1971 - 7 Aug. 1981, (8 p. 3 t.l.s., 2 t.l.) (Box A)
      [Includes two letters in re: Kazan]
    - Kazan, Elia To Tennessee Williams, v.p., n.d. - 14 Sept. 1982, (6 p. 3 t.l.s. & 3 t.l.) (Box A)
      [Includes t.l.s. in re: Kazan and 1 envelope]
    - Kazan, Elia To Tennessee Williams, n.p., 22 Jan. 1959, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [Signed 'Gadg']
    - Kerr, Walter To Tennessee Williams, Larchmont, NY, (ca. 1959), (3 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Kennedy (Onassis), Jacquline Bouvier Kennedy To Tennessee Williams, Washington D.C., 22 May 1962, (1 p. a.n.s. ) (Box A)
    - Ladd, Dianne To Tennessee Williams, New York & Chicago, 1961 & n.d., (9 p. 1 t.l.s. & 1 a.l.s. ) (Box A)
      [Both with envelopes]
    - Laszlo, Eva To Tennessee Williams, Budapest, 12 Dec. 1962, (4 pp. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Laszlo, Eva To Tennessee Williams, Budapest, 18 May 1963, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Laughlin, James To Paul Bigelow, New York, 4 Jan. 1951, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Laughlin, James To Paul Bigelow, New York, 16 Jan. 1951, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Laughlin, James To Tennessee Williams, v.p., 1963 - 1976, (6 p. 5 t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Leigh, Vivien To Tennessee Williams, New York, NY, [May 9, 1966], (1 p. a.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Lemmon, Jack To Elliot Martin, [n.p.], 3 October 1979, (2 p t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [Includes forwarding letter from Elliot Martin to TW]
    - Lowry, Robert To Tennessee Williams, Kings Park, NY, 13 Jan. 1957, (1 p. a.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Magnani, Anna To Tennessee Williams, Rome, Italy, 1958 - 1961, (6 p. 4 t.l.s. 3 telegrams ) (Box A)
    - Magnani, Anna To Tennessee Williams, Rome, Italy, 7 Nov. 1958, (2p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [Text in Italian]
    - Magnani, Anna To Tennessee Williams, Rome, Italy, 26 Jan. 1959, (2 p. telegram) (Box A)
    - Magnani, Anna To Martin Jurow, [n.p.], 31 Jan. 1959, (7 p. t.l.) (Box A)
      [typed copy of letter]
    - Malanga, Gerard To Tennessee Williams, New York, NY, 25 March 1966, (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - McCullers, Carson To Tennessee Williams, v.p., 1943 - 1960, (20 p. 10 a.l.s., 1 t.l.s., 1 telegram ) (Box A)
      [With envelopes]
    - Merlo, Frank To Tennessee Williams, [Key West], [195?], (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Merrick, David To Tennessee Williams, New York, 3 May 1963 - 12 Sept. 1974, (3 p. 2 t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Miller, Arthur To Tennessee Williams, Roxbury, CT, 9 Dec. 1980, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Mrabet, Mohammed To Tennessee Williams, Tangier, Morocco, 30 March 1974, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Nin, Anais To Tennessee Williams, n.p. & New York, n.d. & 14 Dec. 1965, (3 p. 2 t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [One letter from publisher in re: Diary of Anais Nin]
    - Patchen, Kenneth To Tennessee Williams, Palo Alto, CA, 5 Feb. 1960, (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Pinter, Harold To Tennessee Williams, London, England, 25 Oct. 19[??], (1 p. a.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne To Tennessee Williams, Southbury, CT, 25 Jan. 1958, (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Purdy, James To Tennessee Williams, Brooklyn, NY, 12 Sept. 1960, (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Rader, Dotson To Tennessee Williams, v.p., 1971 - 1982, (16 p. 12 t.l.s. 1 a.n.s. 2 telegrams ) (Box A)
      [letter dated Sept. 12, 1973 removed from Williams Book collection]
    - Redgrave, Vanessa To Tennessee Williams, London, England, 10 May 19[??], (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Rorem, Ned To Tennessee Williams, Buffalo, NY, n.d., (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - St. Just, Lady Maria To Tennessee Williams, v.p., 1975 - 1981, (7 p. 3 a.l.s. 4 telegrams ) (Box A)
      [With two picture cards With comments on verso by St. Just and related correspondence]
    - St. Just, Lady Maria To Audrey Wood, London, 12 Aug. 1963, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [With a postscript paragraph in the hand of Lady Maria St. Just]
    - Shatner, William To Tennessee Williams, [Los Angeles, CA], 12 July 1981, (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Simon, Neil To Tennessee Williams, New York, NY, 15 March 1967, (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Sitwell, Edith To Tennessee Williams, New York, NY & London, 10 Oct. 1950 & 31 March 1953, (2 p. a.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Stark, Ray To Tennessee Williams, [n.p.], 7 Oct. 1963, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Stark, Ray To Tennessee Williams, New York, 23 Oct. 1963, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Tynan, Kenneth To Tennessee Williams, London, 15 July 1968, (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Vaccaro, Marion To Tennessee Williams, Miami, 24 May [1963], (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
      [With related letter and envelope]
    - Vaccaro, Marion To Tennessee Williams, [Miami], 2 Oct. [1963], (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Van Doren, Mark To Tennessee Williams, Falls Village, CT, 22 April 1963, (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Wescott, Glenway To Tennessee Williams, New York, 16 Nov. [1950?], (1 p. a.n.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Jonathan To Tennessee Williams, Corn Close, England, 28 Oct. 1981, (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Williams, Rose To Daddy, Vicksburg, MS, 2 Feb. 1926, (3 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Rose To Tennessee Williams, [n.p.], 28 Dec. 1949, (3 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To [?], n.p., n.d., (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [last part of an incomplete letter]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Hubert Creekmore, London, [n.d.], (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Hubert Creekmore, London, [n.d.], (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rev. Walter Edwin Dakin, Rome, Italy, [n.d.], (1 p. a.n.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Josephine Healy, [n.p.], [n.d.], (1 p. a.n.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Josephine Healy, Key West, [n.d.], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Josephine Healy, Rome, Italy, [n.d.], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Pat and Dotson [Rader], n.p., n.d., (2 p. 2 t.l.) (Box A)
      [both t.l. incomplete]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Audrey Wood, n.p., n.d., (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Fritz, n.p., n.d., (1 p. t.l.s. ) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To George, n.p., n.d., (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
      [written on the back of an a.l. from Maggie to TW]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Greg, n.p., n.d., (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Henry, n.p., n.d., (1 p. t.l.) (Box A)
      [unfinished letter]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rose Williams, [Clarksdale, MS], [1920], (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rose Williams, [Clarksdale, MS], [1920], (4 p. a.ms.) (Box A)
      [Rainbow Comic paper illustrated by TW; contained With [1920] letter from TW to Rose]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rose Williams, Clarksdale, MS, 15 March 1920, (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, Clarksdale, MS, 28 Feb. 1920, (3 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
      [With the beginning of another letter on the last page]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Godmother, St. Louis, MO, 13 April 1921, (1 p. a.l.) (Box A)
      [only the first page is present; in folder of a.l.s. by TW to Edwina Williams 28 Feb. 1920]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, Clarksdale, MS, 27 May 1920, (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, Clarksdale, MS, 17 Oct. 1920, (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rose Williams, Clarksdale, MS, 30 Oct. 1920, (4 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rose Williams, St. Louis, MO, [Nov. 1929], (4 p. t.l.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rev. Walter Edwin Dakin, [St. Louis, MO], [Nov. 1929], (2 p. t.l.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rev. Walter Edwin Dakin, [St. Louis, MO], [1929], (1 p. t.l.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rev. Walter Edwin Dakin, [Columbia, MO], [1930], (4 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, [Memphis, TN], 17 Aug. 1935, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, Hollister, MO, 6 Aug. 1936, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Audrey Wood, [Laguna Beach, CA], 29 July 1939, (3 pp. t.l. (photostat)) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, [Mexico City?], 4 Sept. 1940, (1 pp. a.p.c.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Folks, [En route from Boston to New York], [Dec. 1940 - Jan. 1941], (4 pp. a.l.s.) (Box A)
      [letter written by Williams after the opening of Battle of Angels in Boston, With envelope]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Joe, [n.p.], [n.d.], (2 pp. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, New York, [1941], (2 pp. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Folks, Miami, FL, [22 March 1941], (3 pp. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [Provincetown, MA], [25 July 1941], (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Chattanooga, TN, 10 Sept. 1941, (1 pp. a.p.c.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, New Orleans, 25 Sept 1941, (4 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Bay St. Louis, 9 Oct 1941, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [New Orleans], [11 Oct 1941], (4 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [New Orleans], [23 Oct 1941], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Jackson, MS, [3 Nov 1941], (4 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, New Orleans, 18 Dec 1941, (3 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [St. Louis], [5 Jan 1942], (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, St. Simon's Island, GA, 27 Aug 1941, (4 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, New York, [15 May 1942], (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, New York, [5 June 1942], (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [St. Augustine, FL], [14 Aug 1942], (3 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [St. Augustine, FL], [19 Aug 1942], (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, St. Augustine, FL, 23 Aug 1942, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [St. Augustine, FL], [25 Aug 1942], (4 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
      [[With clippings; With envelope]]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [Jacksonville, FL], [28 Aug 1942], (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Jacksonville, FL, 31 Aug 1942, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Jacksonville, FL, [22 Sept 1942], (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
      [[With envelope]]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Robert P. Tristram Coffin, Jacksonville, FL, 5 Oct 1942, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [Jacksonville, FL], [17 Oct 1942], (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box A)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, St. Louis, 2 April 1943, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Culver City, CA, 23 May 1943, (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Culver City, CA, [9 June 1943], (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [With envelope; With clipping]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Culver City, CA, 15 July 1943, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Culver City, CA, 4 Aug 1943, (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, New York, [May 1944], (1 a.n.s.) (Box B)
      [written at bottom of notice from The American Academy of Arts and Letters; With enclosed program and envelope]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [Mexico City?], [8 June 1945], (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Guadalajara, Mexico, [? July 1945?], (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To The Reverend Walter Edwin Dakin, v.p., n.d. - 1946, (1 3 telegrams) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, New Orleans, [27 Feb 1946], (4 p a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Jordan Massee and Paul Bigelow, [New York], [ca. 1947], (3 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [New Orleans], 6 March 1947, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To The Reverend Walter Edwin Dakin, [New Orleans], 29 March 1947, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Paris, 7 Jan. 1948, (3 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [New York], [1948?], (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [n.p.], 7 July 1948, (1 ) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To The Reverend Walter Edwin Dakin, New York, 13 Aug 1948, (4 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Dakin Williams, [Gibralter], [19 Dec 1948], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [With envelope containing docket by Dakin on the reverse]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Dakin Williams, [Gibralter], 9 Dec 1948, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [enclosed With letter to Dakin Williams dated 19 Dec 1948]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [Key West, FL], 4 Dec 1949, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Charlie [Charles K. Feldman?], [Hollywood ?], ca. 1950, (1 p. (draft) a.l.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [Key West, FL], 13 Jan 1950, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Key West, FL, [12] April 1950, (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, New York, 16 Sept 1950, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - [Williams, Tennessee] To Audrey Wood, [New York], ca. Feb 1951, (1 p. (draft) t.l.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Key West, FL, 22 Feb 1951, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Josephine Healy, [Key West, FL], 27 Feb 1951, (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Memphis, TN, 4 Dec 1951, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Memphis, TN, 8 Dec 1951, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To [Paul Bigelow], Miami, Jan 1952, (1 p. t.l.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Key West, FL, 12 Feb 1954, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To John B. Myers, Miami, 15 Mar 1956, (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, New York, [1956?], (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
      [With envelope With a.n.]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, New York, [1956?], (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, Havana, [ca. Aug] 1956, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, London, n.d. 1958, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, [Key West, FL], [Jan 1958], (1 p. a.l.) (Box B)
      [added to t.l.s. from Lawrence S. Kubie]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Josephine Healy, Taormina, Italy, 5 Aug 1958, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, Key West, FL, 25 Nov 1958, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [With draft of reply]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Kenneth Tynan, n.p., [1959], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Elia Kazan, n.p., [Jan ? 1959], (4 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [signed "10"]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Brooks Atkinson, Miami, 20 March 1959, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Josephine Healy, [New York], 23 June 1959, (1 p. t.l.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Carson McCullers, Key West, FL, 6 May 1960, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Frank Merlo, Miami, 2 Jan 1961, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Ted [Kalem], Miami, [1962?], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [not sent?]
    - Williams, Tennessee To [Herbert Machiz], n.p., [Spring 1962], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [signed "10" and With related telegram]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Frederick Nicklaus, [Key West, FL], [6 May 1962], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, [Tangiers, Morocco], 6 June 1962, (1 p. t.l.) (Box B)
      [first page only?]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, [Tangiers, Morocco], 27 June 1962, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, Tangiers, Morocco, [ca. July 1962], (3 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)